Jeremy Broutin



+48 514 865 435







Skills

Business relationship management: ability to engage with both marketing and development teams.

Web programming: ability to read and write JavaScript, HTML and CSS code.

App programming: ability to read ObjC, read and write Swift (iOS app) and Java (Android app) code.

Additional skills: frequent usage of Git and GitHub for version controlling, intermediate level in Photoshop, basic usage of Camtasia (video edition tool).

Google products: expert level in Google Analytics, Tag Manager and AdWords.

Projects

(Google) Lead AdWords Mobile App Promotion expansion in EMEA - January 2015 to present

- Identify technical support gap(s) for Mobile App solutions and shortlist Sales priorities accounts.
- Provide high quality support for technical pitch and implementation to major app players.
- Participate in several App Day/Think App conferences to promote mobile app promotion solutions
- Programs used: ObjC, Java, Swift

(Google) Lead Google Tag Manager product adoption in EMEA - January 2014 to June 2014

- Built internal communication, training and support resources for sales teams in collaboration with several stakeholders.
- Provided client-facing support for technical pitch and product implementation, while educating clients around product abilities and roadmap.
- Overall product adoption increased by 10 points in the region (+17 points in some key market).
- Program used: JavaScript

(Tree-Nation) Manage and expand online global community - March 2010 to July 2010

- Led website community management with 60,000 users and expanded social networks presence on Facebook and Twitter, reinforcing users' interactions with the project/business.
- Participated in website redesign to enhance community focus of the project/business (involving sketching on Photoshop).

Relevant Experience

(Google) Solutions Consultant, Wroclaw (Poland) - November 2013 to present

- Provide strategic and technical consultation for Google advertising tracking solutions.
- Lead new products launches and drive adoption, while gathering clients feedback for product improvements and/or existing bugs.
- Partner with different internal stakeholders to enhance efficiency and quality of the delivered services.

(Google) Previous experiences:

- Google Analytics Technical Support Associate, Wroclaw (Poland) May 2013 to November 2013
- Google AdWords SMB Online Associate, Wroclaw (Poland) July 2011 to May 2013

Education

(Post graduation) Udacity iOS Nanodegree - March 2015 to November 2015

• iOS development online degree (programming language: SWIFT)

(Master) Toulouse Business School, Toulouse (France) - September 2008 to Mai 2011

Major: Online business management

(Bachelor) ISAM Groupe Sup de Co, Amiens (France) - September 2005 to Mai 2008

Major: Marketing

(Erasmus) Jÿvaskÿla University of Applied Sciences, Jÿvaskÿla (Finland) - January 2007 to June 2007

• Degree: High tech businesses management

Hobbies

Sports competition and leisure practice:

- Rugby: Wroclaw Rugby Klub (2 years, Poland), RC Amiens (2 years, Poland)
- Football & Futsal: 5 years as junior (1999-2004), Google FC (1 year, Poland)
- Climbing: indoor and outdoor rock climbing and bouldering (6 months, Poland)

Web reading and learning about new technologies and impact on daily life (cars, domotic, health, social, etc)

• Android Blog, TechCrunch, Wired, VentureBeat